{
  "category": "sports",
  "questions":[
    {
      "question": "2010 Commonwealth Games held in ?",
      "answer":   "B: India",
      "optionA":  "A: Canada",
      "optionB":  "B: India",
      "optionC":  "C: Britian",
      "optionD":  "D: Malaysia"
    },
    {
      "question": "The term“Googly” is associated with ?",
      "answer":   "A: Cricket",
      "optionA":  "A: Cricket",
      "optionB":  "B: Football",
      "optionC":  "C: Badminton",
      "optionD":  "D: Hockey"
    },
    {
      "question": "Aga Khan Cup is awarded to ?",
      "answer":   "C: National Hockey in India",
      "optionA":  "A: International Hockey",
      "optionB":  "B: Asian Hockey",
      "optionC":  "C: National Hockey in India",
      "optionD":  "D: None of these"
    },
    {
      "question": "Krishna Poonia is associated with ?",
      "answer":   "C: Chess",
      "optionA":  "A: Football",
      "optionB":  "B: Hockey",
      "optionC":  "C: Chess",
      "optionD":  "D: Athletics"
    },
    {
      "question": "In 1924 the first winter Olympics was held in ?",
      "answer":   "B: France",
      "optionA":  "A: Italy",
      "optionB":  "B: France",
      "optionC":  "C: Austria",
      "optionD":  "D: Canada"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the national sport of Canada? ",
      "answer":   "A: Lacrosse/Ice hockey",
      "optionA":  "A: Lacrosse/Ice hockey",
      "optionB":  "B: Cricket",
      "optionC":  "C: Field hockey",
      "optionD":  "D: Volleyball"
    },
    {
      "question": "Archery is the national sport of which country?",
      "answer":   "B: Bhutan",
      "optionA":  "A: Afghanistan",
      "optionB":  "B: Bhutan",
      "optionC":  "C: Japan",
      "optionD":  "D: India"
    },
    {
      "question": "____________ has Cricket as its national sports.",
      "answer":   "B: Jamaica",
      "optionA":  "A: India",
      "optionB":  "B: Jamaica",
      "optionC":  "C: Sri Lanka",
      "optionD":  "D: United States"
    },
    {
      "question": "_____________ is the national sport of Turkey",
      "answer":   "A: Wrestling",
      "optionA":  "A: Wrestling",
      "optionB":  "B: Rugby union",
      "optionC":  "C: Golf",
      "optionD":  "D: Basketball"
    },
    {
      "question": "When was the Commonwealth game started?",
      "answer":   "A: 1930",
      "optionA":  "A: 1930",
      "optionB":  "B: 1934",
      "optionC":  "C: 1938",
      "optionD":  "D: 1950"
    },

    {
      "question": "Which was the host country in 1998 for Asian Games?",
      "answer":   "A: Thailand",
      "optionA":  "A: Thailand",
      "optionB":  "B: Philippines",
      "optionC":  "C: South Korea",
      "optionD":  "D: China"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which city has hosted Asian Games in 2006?",
      "answer":   "D: Doha",
      "optionA":  "A: Tokyo",
      "optionB":  "B: Bangkok",
      "optionC":  "C: New Delhi",
      "optionD":  "D: Doha"
    },
    {
      "question": "First Olympic Games was held in ________",
      "answer":   "C: Canada",
      "optionA":  "A: England",
      "optionB":  "B: Australia",
      "optionC":  "C: Canada",
      "optionD":  "D: Jamacia"
    },
    {
      "question": "If we are using the following words in a game: Break, Cannons, Cue, In off, Jigger, Scratch. Which game are we playing?",
      "answer":   "B: Billiards",
      "optionA":  "A: Bridge",
      "optionB":  "B: Billiards",
      "optionC":  "C: Polo",
      "optionD":  "D: Baseball"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was the winner of Football World Cup in 2010?",
      "answer":   "D: Spain",
      "optionA":  "A: Italy",
      "optionB":  "B: Brazil",
      "optionC":  "C: France",
      "optionD":  "D: Spain"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following terms is used in the game of Lawn Tennis?",
      "answer":   "A: Deuce",
      "optionA":  "A: Deuce",
      "optionB":  "B: Jockey",
      "optionC":  "C: Punter",
      "optionD":  "D: Scoop"
    },
    {
      "question": "The term 'Tee' is connected with",
      "answer":   "B: Golf",
      "optionA":  "A: Badminton",
      "optionB":  "B: Golf",
      "optionC":  "C: Bridge",
      "optionD":  "D: Polo"
    },
    {
      "question": "The name of the Mascot for 1996 Olympics held at Atlanta was",
      "answer":   "C: SWHATZ IT",
      "optionA":  "A: Matari",
      "optionB":  "B: APPU",
      "optionC":  "C: SWHATZ IT",
      "optionD":  "D: Uncle Sam"
    },
    {
      "question": "The Olympic museum was opened at which of the following places?",
      "answer":   "A: Lausanne",
      "optionA":  "A: Lausanne",
      "optionB":  "B: Istanbul",
      "optionC":  "C: Athens",
      "optionD":  "D: Rome"
    },
    {
      "question": "'Ashes' is the term associates with which sports?",
      "answer":   "B: Cricket",
      "optionA":  "A: Basketball",
      "optionB":  "B: Cricket",
      "optionC":  "C: Hockey",
      "optionD":  "D: Volleyball"
    },

    {
      "question": "The term 'Butterfly Stroke' is associated with",
      "answer":   "D: Swimming",
      "optionA":  "A: Wrestling",
      "optionB":  "B: Boxing",
      "optionC":  "C: Kabaddi",
      "optionD":  "D: Swimming"
    },
    {
      "question": "Prakash Padukone is associated with which games?",
      "answer":   "D: Badminton",
      "optionA":  "A: Cricket",
      "optionB":  "B: Table Tennis",
      "optionC":  "C: Judo",
      "optionD":  "D: Badminton"
    },
    {
      "question": "Major R.S. Brar is associated with",
      "answer":   "C: Equestrian",
      "optionA":  "A: Boxing",
      "optionB":  "B: Golf",
      "optionC":  "C: Equestrian",
      "optionD":  "D: Tennis"
    },
    {
      "question": "Crame Trophy Tennis final held in May 2003 was played between",
      "answer":   "C: Boris Becker and John McEnroe",
      "optionA":  "A: Leander Paes and David Rickle",
      "optionB":  "B: John McEnore and David Rickle",
      "optionC":  "C: Boris Becker and John McEnroe",
      "optionD":  "D: Boris Becker and Leander Paes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following games originated from England?",
      "answer":   "C: Cricket",
      "optionA":  "A: Baseball",
      "optionB":  "B: Archery",
      "optionC":  "C: Cricket",
      "optionD":  "D: Hockey"
    },
    {
      "question": "Grand Slam in Tennis means a player has to win",
      "answer":   "A: Australian open, French open, U.S. open and Wimbledon",
      "optionA":  "A: Australian open, French open, U.S. open and Wimbledon",
      "optionB":  "B: Australian open, U.S. Open and Wimbledon",
      "optionC":  "C: Australian open, French open and Wimbledon",
      "optionD":  "D: French open, Wimbledon"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who won the maximum number of gold medals in Hiroshima Asian Games?",
      "answer":   "A: China",
      "optionA":  "A: China",
      "optionB":  "B: India",
      "optionC":  "C: South Korea",
      "optionD":  "D: Japan"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the length of each stump in the cricket?",
      "answer":   "C: 28 inches",
      "optionA":  "A: 35 inches",
      "optionB":  "B: 22 inches",
      "optionC":  "C: 28 inches",
      "optionD":  "D: 33 inches"
    },
    {
      "question": "If you scored a cannon, which game would you be playing?",
      "answer":   "B: Billiards",
      "optionA":  "A: football",
      "optionB":  "B: Billiards",
      "optionC":  "C: Cricket",
      "optionD":  "D: Hockey"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many players are there in Water Polo team?",
      "answer":   "D: 7",
      "optionA":  "A: 4",
      "optionB":  "B: 5",
      "optionC":  "C: 6",
      "optionD":  "D: 7"
    },

    {
      "question": "Who was the first non-European to win the Ballon d'Or?",
      "answer":   "C: George Weah",
      "optionA":  "A: Ronaldo",
      "optionB":  "B: Pelé",
      "optionC":  "C: George Weah",
      "optionD":  "D: Rivaldo"
    },
    {
      "question": "Rangers have been Scottish league champions 54 times. With which club did they share the title in 1890–91?",
      "answer":   "C: Dumbarton",
      "optionA":  "A: Celtic",
      "optionB":  "B: Aberdeen",
      "optionC":  "C: Dumbarton",
      "optionD":  "D: Dundee United"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the score in the Euro 2012 final?",
      "answer":   "B: 4-0",
      "optionA":  "A: 5-0",
      "optionB":  "B: 4-0",
      "optionC":  "C: 3-0",
      "optionD":  "D: 2-0"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who won the man of the match award for the 2014 World Cup final?",
      "answer":   "A: Mario Götze",
      "optionA":  "A: Mario Götze",
      "optionB":  "B: Sergio Romero",
      "optionC":  "C: Martín Demichelis",
      "optionD":  "D: Lionel Messi"
    },
    {
      "question": "The 2022 World Cup will be held in Qatar. Name the only other side to host the tournament without previously competing in the competition?",
      "answer":   "C: Uruguay",
      "optionA":  "A: South Africa",
      "optionB":  "B: Switzerland",
      "optionC":  "C: Uruguay",
      "optionD":  "D: Chile"
    },
    {
      "question": "Against which country did Wayne Rooney break the England goalscoring record?",
      "answer":   "B: Switzerland",
      "optionA":  "A: Slovenia",
      "optionB":  "B: Switzerland",
      "optionC":  "C: Lithuania",
      "optionD":  "D: San Marino"
    },
    {
      "question": "Former Ballon d'Or winner Andriy Shevchenko is from which nation?",
      "answer":   "D: Ukraine",
      "optionA":  "A: Belarus",
      "optionB":  "B: Russia",
      "optionC":  "C: Estonia",
      "optionD":  "D: Ukraine"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is width of goal post in the game of football?",
      "answer":   "C: 24 feet",
      "optionA":  "A: 20 feet",
      "optionB":  "B: 22 feet",
      "optionC":  "C: 24 feet",
      "optionD":  "D: 26 feet"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the goal-keeper who played in five Football World Cup tournaments?",
      "answer":   "B: Antonio Carbajal",
      "optionA":  "A: Gerd Muller",
      "optionB":  "B: Antonio Carbajal",
      "optionC":  "C: Bryan Robson",
      "optionD":  "D: Lothar Matthaeus"
    },
    {
      "question": "“Bull’s eye” is used in the game of",
      "answer":   "A: Shooting",
      "optionA":  "A: Shooting",
      "optionB":  "B: Boxing",
      "optionC":  "C: Polo",
      "optionD":  "D: Baseball"
    },

    {
      "question": "What is the distance between the popping crease and the stumps on a cricket pitch?",
      "answer":   "D: 4 feet",
      "optionA":  "A: 2 ½ feet",
      "optionB":  "B: 3 feet",
      "optionC":  "C: 3 ½ feet",
      "optionD":  "D: 4 feet"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jahangir Khan is famous in which sport?",
      "answer":   "A: Squash",
      "optionA":  "A: Squash",
      "optionB":  "B: Boxing",
      "optionC":  "C: Cricket",
      "optionD":  "D: Hockey"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following terms is not associated with Foot-ball?",
      "answer":   "C: Penalty Kick",
      "optionA":  "A: Free Kick",
      "optionB":  "B: Off Side",
      "optionC":  "C: Penalty Kick",
      "optionD":  "D: Penalty Stroke"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which cricketer holds the record for scoring highest number of runs in a test match innings?",
      "answer":   "A: Brian Lara",
      "optionA":  "A: Brian Lara",
      "optionB":  "B: Sunil Gavaskar",
      "optionC":  "C: Gary Sobers",
      "optionD":  "D: Vivian Richards"
    },
    {
      "question": "Serena Williams is one of the top ranked sportswomen of",
      "answer":   "B: Tennis",
      "optionA":  "A: Chess",
      "optionB":  "B: Tennis",
      "optionC":  "C: Shooting",
      "optionD":  "D: Badminton"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the first of the four Grand slam tennis tournaments to be held each year?",
      "answer":   "D: Australian open",
      "optionA":  "A: U.S. Open",
      "optionB":  "B: Wimbledon",
      "optionC":  "C: French Open",
      "optionD":  "D: Australian open"
    },
    {
      "question": "‘Lay-up shot’ is a term associated with which of the following games?",
      "answer":   "B: Basketball",
      "optionA":  "A: Handball",
      "optionB":  "B: Basketball",
      "optionC":  "C: Throw ball",
      "optionD":  "D: Volleyball"
    },
    {
      "question": "‘Subroto Cup’ is associated with which game/sports?",
      "answer":   "B: Football",
      "optionA":  "A: Hockey",
      "optionB":  "B: Football",
      "optionC":  "C: Basketball",
      "optionD":  "D: Badminton"
    },
    {
      "question": "Rangaswami Cup is associated with",
      "answer":   "B: Hockey",
      "optionA":  "A: Golf",
      "optionB":  "B: Hockey",
      "optionC":  "C: Football",
      "optionD":  "D: Wrestling"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many players are there on each side in the game of basketball?",
      "answer":   "A: 5",
      "optionA":  "A: 5",
      "optionB":  "B: 6",
      "optionC":  "C: 7",
      "optionD":  "D: 8"
    },

    {
      "question": "Which of the following trophies is not awarded in cricket?",
      "answer":   "B: Ryder Cup",
      "optionA":  "A: Ashes",
      "optionB":  "B: Ryder Cup",
      "optionC":  "C: Ranji Trophy",
      "optionD":  "D: Deodhar Trophy"
    },
    {
      "question": "2018 FIFA World Cup would be held in",
      "answer":   "C: Russia",
      "optionA":  "A: Qatar",
      "optionB":  "B: France",
      "optionC":  "C: Russia",
      "optionD":  "D: Netherlands"
    },
    {
      "question": "The term ‘Pitcher’ is associated with:",
      "answer":   "B: Baseball",
      "optionA":  "A: Basketball",
      "optionB":  "B: Baseball",
      "optionC":  "C: Boxing",
      "optionD":  "D: Wrestling"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following International Tennis Tournaments is not held at the same venue year after year?",
      "answer":   "A: Davis Cup",
      "optionA":  "A: Davis Cup",
      "optionB":  "B: U.S. Open",
      "optionC":  "C: French Open",
      "optionD":  "D: Australian open"
    },
    {
      "question": "The first World Cup in cricket was held in",
      "answer":   "C: 1975",
      "optionA":  "A: 1971",
      "optionB":  "B: 1973",
      "optionC":  "C: 1975",
      "optionD":  "D: 1977"
    },
    {
      "question": "The word “Jump ball” is associated with",
      "answer":   "B: Basketbal",
      "optionA":  "A: Softball",
      "optionB":  "B: Basketbal",
      "optionC":  "C: Netball",
      "optionD":  "D: Baseball"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where did the game of Chess originate?",
      "answer":   "A: India",
      "optionA":  "A: India",
      "optionB":  "B: Persia",
      "optionC":  "C: Arabia",
      "optionD":  "D: Europe"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nine time Wimbledon Champion of Women’s Singles Match in Tennis is:",
      "answer":   "C: Martina Navratilova",
      "optionA":  "A: Iva Majoli",
      "optionB":  "B: Jana Novotna",
      "optionC":  "C: Martina Navratilova",
      "optionD":  "D: Mary Joe Fernandaz"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who won the goal medal for 400 meters run at two consecutive Olympic Games?",
      "answer":   "B: Michael Johnson",
      "optionA":  "A: Carl Lawis",
      "optionB":  "B: Michael Johnson",
      "optionC":  "C: Gregory Haughton",
      "optionD":  "D: Alvin Harrison"
    },
    {
      "question": "‘Free throw’ is associated with:",
      "answer":   "A: Basketball",
      "optionA":  "A: Basketball",
      "optionB":  "B: Hockey",
      "optionC":  "C: Volleyball",
      "optionD":  "D: Football"
    },

    {
      "question": "Badminton is National game of which country?",
      "answer":   "D: Malaysia",
      "optionA":  "A: Russia",
      "optionB":  "B: Japan",
      "optionC":  "C: India",
      "optionD":  "D: Malaysia"
    },
    {
      "question": "The number of players on each side in baseball is _______",
      "answer":   "C: Nine",
      "optionA":  "A: Seven",
      "optionB":  "B: Eight",
      "optionC":  "C: Nine",
      "optionD":  "D: Ten"
    },
    {
      "question": "'Cue ball, break shot, pool table' are terms associated with which of the following games?",
      "answer":   "A: Billiards",
      "optionA":  "A: Billiards",
      "optionB":  "B: Football",
      "optionC":  "C: Cricket",
      "optionD":  "D: Squash"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which batsman started his international cricketing career at the age of 16?",
      "answer":   "D: Sachin Tendulkar",
      "optionA":  "A: Kapil Dev",
      "optionB":  "B: Piyush Chawla",
      "optionC":  "C: Rahul Dravid",
      "optionD":  "D: Sachin Tendulkar"
    },
    {
      "question": "A Kabaddi team usually has ______",
      "answer":   "C: Seven players",
      "optionA":  "A: Nine players",
      "optionB":  "B: Eleven players",
      "optionC":  "C: Seven players",
      "optionD":  "D: Eight players"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Indian cricketer has written the book, ‘One Day Wonders’?",
      "answer":   "B: Sunil Gavaskar",
      "optionA":  "A: Kapil Dev",
      "optionB":  "B: Sunil Gavaskar",
      "optionC":  "C: Ravi Shastri",
      "optionD":  "D: Sachin Tendulkar"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which player got stripped of his seven Tour de France titles and got banned for life by the International Cycling Union?",
      "answer":   "D: Lance Armstrong",
      "optionA":  "A: Chris Hoy",
      "optionB":  "B: Nicola Adams",
      "optionC":  "C: Jason Kenny",
      "optionD":  "D: Lance Armstrong"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not correct?",
      "answer":   "B: Jeev Milkha Singh (Football)",
      "optionA":  "A: Sania Mirza (Tennis)",
      "optionB":  "B: Jeev Milkha Singh (Football)",
      "optionC":  "C: Saina Nehwal (Badminton)",
      "optionD":  "D: Vishwanathan Anand (Chess)"
    },
    {
      "question": "The famous woman Tennis player, who was stabbed during a match, is",
      "answer":   "C: Monica Seles",
      "optionA":  "A: Mary Pierce",
      "optionB":  "B: Steffi Graf",
      "optionC":  "C: Monica Seles",
      "optionD":  "D: Aranta Sanchez Vicario"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the athlete who set the maximum number (6) of the world records in a span of 45 minutes?",
      "answer":   "D: “Jesse” (John Cleveland) Owens",
      "optionA":  "A: Carl Lewis",
      "optionB":  "B: Michael Johnson",
      "optionC":  "C: Florence G. Joyner",
      "optionD":  "D: “Jesse” (John Cleveland) Owens"
    },

    {
      "question": "For which game Tiger Woods is famous?",
      "answer":   "A: Golf",
      "optionA":  "A: Golf",
      "optionB":  "B: Football",
      "optionC":  "C: Pole-vault",
      "optionD":  "D: Basketball"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nehru Trophy is associated with",
      "answer":   "A: Football",
      "optionA":  "A: Football",
      "optionB":  "B: Kabbadi",
      "optionC":  "C: Hockey",
      "optionD":  "D: Table Tennis (Women)"
    },
    {
      "question": "The first women to swim across seven important seas is:",
      "answer":   "C: Bula Choudhary",
      "optionA":  "A: Chandini",
      "optionB":  "B: Mridula Rajiv",
      "optionC":  "C: Bula Choudhary",
      "optionD":  "D: Priya Shanbhag"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which one of the following players has the unique distinction of winning 50 Doubles Titles in A.T.P. tour history?",
      "answer":   "A: Leander Paes",
      "optionA":  "A: Leander Paes",
      "optionB":  "B: Andy Roddick",
      "optionC":  "C: Rafael Nadal",
      "optionD":  "D: Novae Djokovic"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who made history by winning 8 gold medals in the Beijing Olympics in one event?",
      "answer":   "B: Michael Phelps of U.S.A.",
      "optionA":  "A: Ian Kraken of U.S.A.",
      "optionB":  "B: Michael Phelps of U.S.A.",
      "optionC":  "C: Van Lee Chu of China",
      "optionD":  "D: Marcus Michael of France"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many outstanding cricket players have been awarded the Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna Award so far?",
      "answer":   "C: Two (2)",
      "optionA":  "A: Nil",
      "optionB":  "B: One only",
      "optionC":  "C: Two (2)",
      "optionD":  "D: Five (5)"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who among the following bowlers has taken more than 500 wickets in Test cricket?",
      "answer":   "C: Glenn McGrath",
      "optionA":  "A: Kapil Dev",
      "optionB":  "B: Wasim Akram",
      "optionC":  "C: Glenn McGrath",
      "optionD":  "D: Malcolm Marshall"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lionel Messi, the winner of FIFA Ballion d’or and World Player of the year, belongs to",
      "answer":   "D: Argentina",
      "optionA":  "A: Spain",
      "optionB":  "B: Brazil",
      "optionC":  "C: Germany",
      "optionD":  "D: Argentina"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following International Tennis Tournaments is held on grass court?",
      "answer":   "D: Wimbledon",
      "optionA":  "A: French Open",
      "optionB":  "B: U.S. Open",
      "optionC":  "C: Australian open",
      "optionD":  "D: Wimbledon"
    },
    {
      "question": "Name the sportsman who has made maximum centuries in one day cricket.",
      "answer":   "C: Sachin Tendulkar",
      "optionA":  "A: Brian Lara",
      "optionB":  "B: Saeed Anwar",
      "optionC":  "C: Sachin Tendulkar",
      "optionD":  "D: Vivian Richards"
    },

    {
      "question": "With which game is Geet Sethi associated?",
      "answer":   "D: Billiards",
      "optionA":  "A: Squash",
      "optionB":  "B: Kabbadi",
      "optionC":  "C: Lawn Tennis",
      "optionD":  "D: Billiards"
    },
    {
      "question": "Developed as a less strenuous alternative to basketball which game was invented in 1895 by William Morgan?",
      "answer":   "B: Volleyball",
      "optionA":  "A: Netball",
      "optionB":  "B: Volleyball",
      "optionC":  "C: Throwball",
      "optionD":  "D: Softball"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which sports is the participant called pugilist?",
      "answer":   "B: Boxing",
      "optionA":  "A: Sprinter",
      "optionB":  "B: Boxing",
      "optionC":  "C: Wrestling",
      "optionD":  "D: Javelin throw"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who finished 10th in the 2014/15 Premier League?",
      "answer":   "A: Crystal Palace",
      "optionA":  "A: Crystal Palace",
      "optionB":  "B: Stoke",
      "optionC":  "C: Everton",
      "optionD":  "D: West Ham"
    },
    {
      "question": "Track and field star Carl Lewis won how many gold medals at the 1984 Olympic games?",
      "answer":   "C: Four",
      "optionA":  "A: Two",
      "optionB":  "B: Three",
      "optionC":  "C: Four",
      "optionD":  "D: Eight"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which county did Ravi Shastri play for?",
      "answer":   "A: Glamorgan",
      "optionA":  "A: Glamorgan",
      "optionB":  "B: Leicestershire",
      "optionC":  "C: Gloucestershire",
      "optionD":  "D: Lancashire"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which two counties did Kapil Dev play?",
      "answer":   "A: Northamptonshire & Worcestershire",
      "optionA":  "A: Northamptonshire & Worcestershire",
      "optionB":  "B: Northamptonshire & Warwickshire",
      "optionC":  "C: Nottinghamshire & Worcestershire",
      "optionD":  "D: Nottinghamshire & Warwickshire"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who did Stone Cold Steve Austin wrestle at the 1998 edition of 'Over the Edge'?",
      "answer":   "C: Dude Love",
      "optionA":  "A: Cactus Jack",
      "optionB":  "B: Mankind",
      "optionC":  "C: Dude Love",
      "optionD":  "D: Mick Foley"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ricky Ponting is also known as what?",
      "answer":   "D: Punter",
      "optionA":  "A: The Rickster",
      "optionB":  "B: Ponts",
      "optionC":  "C: Ponter",
      "optionD":  "D: Punter"
    },
    {
      "question": "How long are professional Golf Tour players allotted per shot?",
      "answer":   "A: 45 seconds",
      "optionA":  "A: 45 seconds",
      "optionB":  "B: 25 seconds",
      "optionC":  "C: 1 minute",
      "optionD":  "D: 2 minutes"
    },

    {
      "question": "Which NBA player scored 8 points in the final 7 seconds of a game to lead his team to victory?",
      "answer":   "D: Reggie Miller",
      "optionA":  "A: Baron Davis",
      "optionB":  "B: Kevin Garnett",
      "optionC":  "C: Stephon Maurbury",
      "optionD":  "D: Reggie Miller"
    },
    {
      "question": "The first hang gliders to be flown were flown in?",
      "answer":   "C: 1800s",
      "optionA":  "A: 1600s",
      "optionB":  "B: 1700s",
      "optionC":  "C: 1800s",
      "optionD":  "D: 1900s"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who won the 1993 'King of the Ring'?",
      "answer":   "B: Bret Hart",
      "optionA":  "A: Owen Hart",
      "optionB":  "B: Bret Hart",
      "optionC":  "C: Edge",
      "optionD":  "D: Mabel"
    },
    {
      "question": "What Major League Baseball player holds the record for all-time career high batting average?",
      "answer":   "A: Ty Cobb",
      "optionA":  "A: Ty Cobb",
      "optionB":  "B: Larry Walker",
      "optionC":  "C: Jeff Bagwell",
      "optionD":  "D: Frank Thomas"
    },
    {
      "question": " Undertaker wrestled in Casket Match at the 1998 'Royal Rumble'. Who did he wrestle?",
      "answer":   "B: Shawn Michaels",
      "optionA":  "A: Yokozuna",
      "optionB":  "B: Shawn Michaels",
      "optionC":  "C: Mabel",
      "optionD":  "D: Triple H"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the highest wicket taker in Test cricket?",
      "answer":   "D: Muttiah Muralitharan",
      "optionA":  "A: Shane Warne",
      "optionB":  "B: Brian Lara",
      "optionC":  "C: Courtney Walsh",
      "optionD":  "D: Muttiah Muralitharan"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who did The Rock wrestle in the main event at the 1999 edition of 'Wrestlemania'?",
      "answer":   "A: Stone Cold Steve Austin",
      "optionA":  "A: Stone Cold Steve Austin",
      "optionB":  "B: Triple H",
      "optionC":  "C: Mankind",
      "optionD":  "D: Undertaker"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which track and field star overcame childhood polio to become one of the greatest athletes of her time?",
      "answer":   "A: Wilma Rudolph",
      "optionA":  "A: Wilma Rudolph",
      "optionB":  "B: Gail Devers",
      "optionC":  "C: Florence Griffith Joyner",
      "optionD":  "D: Jackie Robinson"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which football hero was nicknamed 'The Sundance Kid'?",
      "answer":   "A: Jim Kiick",
      "optionA":  "A: Jim Kiick",
      "optionB":  "B: Troy Aikman",
      "optionC":  "C: Brett Favre",
      "optionD":  "D: Joe Montana"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who did Shawn Michaels beat to win his first Intercontinental Title?",
      "answer":   "C: British Bulldog",
      "optionA":  "A: Bret Hart",
      "optionB":  "B: Marty Jannetty",
      "optionC":  "C: British Bulldog",
      "optionD":  "D: Tito Santana"
    }


  ]
}